themelgroup.co.uk 2011-05-13

# The MEL Group

MEL Aviation Ltd takes your privacy very seriously. Please read this Policy carefully to see how we will treat the personal information that you provide to us when using our Site. We will take reasonable care to keep your information secure and to prevent any unauthorised access or use of it. We process all information in accordance with the applicable UK data protection legislation. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and the change will take effect once the revised Privacy Policy is available on our homepage. Please refer to this policy each time you submit your personal information. 

**The information you provide**  
We may ask you to provide information at a number of points on the site, such as when you:

1\. E-Mail enquiries to us  
2\. Register to receive information

The information that you are asked to provide will vary depending on the reason for the collection. In some instances, for example, if you purchase goods or services from us, the provision of certain information will be mandatory. 

**How MEL Aviation Ltd uses the information  
**MEL Aviation Ltd will use your personal information only to. We will use your personal information to:

1\. Respond to your enquiry  
2\. Send information to you  
3\. Fulfil any contract that we may enter into with you

**Links**   
Our Site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware of this when they leave our Site, and to read the privacy statements on those sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on this Site.

**Your right to access the information**  
You have the right to access the information that MEL Aviation Ltd holds about you. To do this, please make a written application to the Data Protection Officer, at the address given below. MEL Aviation Ltd may require you to provide verification of your identity and to pay an administrative fee (currently £10) to provide a copy of the information that it holds. In certain circumstances MEL Aviation Ltd may withhold access to your information where it has the right to do so under current data protection legislation.

**Updating your information**   
In the event that there is a change to your personal information, for example your contact details, please let us know of this by writing to the Data Protection Officer, at the address below so that we can keep your information up to date and accurate.

**Contact us**  
If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy, or you wish to stop direct marketing by MEL Aviation Ltd or its subsidiaries, or you wish to access or update your information, please write to the:

Data Protection Officer  
MEL Aviation Ltd  
Laurence Walter House  
Addison Road  
Chilton Industrial Estate   
Sudbury, Suffolk  
England  
CO10 2YW 

MEL Aviation Ltd 25th October 2004.
